http://www.snapnetwork.org/privacy

Privacy
If you have any questions/corrections about your privacy please contact: accounts@snapnetwork.org
Home
Privacy
Share
Online Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When donating or registering on our site as appropriate your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.
You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To update you on latest SNAP developments (Your information helps us more effectively provide you with the latest news on the continuing work of SNAP, respond to your requests or other support needs)
To process donations: Your information, whether public or private will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send information, respond to your enquiries, annual appeals, and or other requests/questions
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures  in order to maintain the safety of your personal information when you  enter, submit or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied/sensitive credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and then encrypted into our Payment Gateway Provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special rights to such systems, and we are required to keep the information confidential.
Do we disclose information to any outside parties?
We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal identifiable information. This does not include third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirement of COPPA(Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website and associated information is directed to people who are at least 13 years old and older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:
SNAPP.O. Box 56539St. Louis, MO 63156USA314-776-9277www.SNAPNetwork.org
Spread the Word!
Sign in if you'd like new recruits to be credited to you.
Share
Tweet
Email
Donate
Report Abuse to your AG
Share Your Story
Get Help Now
Locations
SNAPNetwork
Join our mailing list!
Protect the vulnerable. Heal the wounded. Prevent the abuse.
Optional email code
Survivor
Supporter
Send me email updates
Send me text message updates
CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongo, the Democratic Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran, Islamic Republic ofIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorth Macedonia, Republic ofNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da CunhaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela, Bolivarian Republic ofViet NamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Donate
Share
